Gleb: It is about time!
Gleb: Iden Versio. The Admiral sent you. I knew I was important, but to risk his own daughter's life?
Iden: Target acquired. Get a move on Gleb.
Gleb: She is giving me orders now. Precious.
Hask: Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa! Get back!
Gleb: No, he is with me. The others will stay here. They are not important. Come!
Del: Commander.
Del: We have a ship on Landing Bay 2. You'll be safe there. Go. Go now. Go!
Hask: Whoa whoa, what are you- no, stop!
Iden: Hask!
Hask: Stop! This is not our mission.
Iden: Stand down.
Iden: It's okay. We'll get you off world. Go.
Hask: No. No. No. Don't you...
Iden: I am your Commander, stand down!
Hask: Iden, our orders are clear. We are to recover the Protectorate Gleb alone.
Del: Things have changed. Look around you, man. Do you even recognize the Empire anymore?
Hask: Del, please don't do this. Just don't do this.
Iden: The Empire's job is to save civilians from things like Operation: Cinder.
Hask: This is the new Empire.
Del: If this is the new Empire I want no part of it. I'm taking the orders of my commanding officer.
Hask: Are these your orders? Are these your orders? Because if they are this is treason.
Hask: Are these your orders?
Iden: Yes.
Hask: Then I have mine.
Iden: Lower your weapon.
Hask: Defiance will be the death of you.
Hask: Agh!
Hask: Admiral Versio
Hask: Commander Versio and Agent Meeko have abandoned the mission. They have committed treason. I'm sorry.
Garrick: Understood. Return Gleb to me, that is your mission. I will take care of the traitors.